maxpedition.com 2017-04-02

# Privacy & Security - MAXPEDITION

### Join Our Mailing List

PRIVACY POLICY OF MAXPEDITION.COM  
  
At Maxpedition.com, the protection of your privacy is of utmost importance and your personal information is guarded as if it were our own. Any information you volunteer through the registration or purchasing process is used only within our company for billing, shipping, and marketing purposes and to improve the content of our website and our service to you. We will never sell, rent, loan, share, trade, give away, or in any way disseminate your personal information to any third part for any purpose whatsoever.

As you browse Maxpedition.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, [AdRoll](http://www.adroll.com/), then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Maxpedition. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit this [page](http://www.adroll.com/) to opt out of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising.  
  
If you supply us with your email through Maxpedition.com, you may receive periodic email messages containing information about new products and services or upcoming events. All mailing list messages contain instructions for unsubscribing.  
  
If you supply us with your postal address through Maxpedition.com, you may receive periodic catalog or brochure mailings from us about new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings or wish to stop receiving future catalogs or would like to report duplicate mailings, please inform us immediately.  
  
If you supply us with your phone number, you will only receive telephone contact from us with questions or information regarding orders that you have placed online.  
  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding any of the above terms of our Privacy Policy, please contact us immediately.

Via Email  
  
Via Telephone  
(310) 768-0098  
  
Via Fax  
(310) 515-5950  
  
Via U.S. Mail  
P.O. Box 5008, Palos Verdes, CA 90274 U.S.A.
